So. you're the cop?
Ex cop.
Jesus Christ!
It's happening
all over London.
So far. we have
over 300 fatalities.
but that figure's bound to rise.
This is the man we believe brought
this cocaine into the country.
The police will make our
lives hell for what happened.
That cocaine was
deliberately spiked.
By whom?
That's what
I intend to find out.
I'm gonna make them pay.
You boys is trespassing.
Phone. There's
only one number.
Call it.
Sean?
Last night's spiking
was Sean's doing.
and someone on the
outside helped him.
We still going ahead with this?
Oh. yeah.
Recognise
him? Tell me his name.
That was your wife?
It wasn't a hit and a run.
Tell me or I'll
fucking kill you!
Sean!
Come on. boy.
Sean. it's all right. It's us.
Come on.
son. We gotta go.
- Jesus.
- This way.
Come on.
All units. Code 2.
I repeat. a Code 2. Officers
down. Seven dead. One injured...
You.
stay here. Let's go.
You set everything
up. like I said?
All done. Money. guns.
We're going to the
helicopter now.
London won't know
what fucking hit it.
What the fuck's...
Block! Point! Driver!
What's going on?
Fucking Albanians! Lay down.
There's a grey BMW.
Round the block.
Key's under the front wing.
You get it started.
we'll follow you. Go on.
Go!
Go. go. go. go!
Whoa.
Hey.
Fuck off.
Sean!
I'm only interested in the man
that killed Naomi and Samuel
and who ordered it.
You give me his name.
I'll help you get away.
Listen!
I meant what I said.
You tell me what I need to know.
I'll help you get
out of the city.
I'll tell you.
If you help me first.
Sean! Sean!
Tell Luan I said no one
touches Sean Wallace!
Where's Sean?
He's not here.
We can't leave without him.
We gotta go.
We gotta go fucking now!
He'll meet us at the helicopter.
Okay?
We have a
man severely injured.
He's one of the gang members.
Multiple
gunshot wounds on trauma one.
On the way to hospital. Over.
Don't worry. You're
gonna be okay.
What are you doing? We've got...
Switch on your
siren. Start driving.
Now.
Okay.
- Hey.
- Oh. shit.
Hey. Hey.
You want to earn
some money. mate?
I don't know you. bruv.
Ten grand. I'll
give you ten grand.
You what?
Fuck off. big man.
before I call the mandem.
Hey. listen. Do you know
who Sean Wallace is?
That's me. I'm Sean
Wallace. Check your phone.
I'm all over the Internet.
If you help me now. I'll
give you ten thousand pounds.
Help you how?
I need some money to get
across London. Two hundred.
I need it now.
If I help you. I want twenty G.
Twenty grand.
All right. follow me.
Open up.
You wait here.
Smoke him. Giddy. Do it.
Just be calm.
Don't you fucking move.
If you kill me now.
you'll lose twenty grand.
We're not losing nothing. bitch.
There's two mill on your head.
What do you mean?
The Albanians. you know?
'Cause you poisoned
all that gear.
Nah. I didn't poison anything.
I had nothing to do with that.
Four million. I'll
give you four million.
Listen
to this wasteman.
Begging for coin and then
acting like he's a millionaire.
You know who my
family are. don't you?
I'm a fucking Wallace.
you know that. right?
All I know is that
you're my payday.
But right now. smoke him. Giddy.
Or give me the skeng
and I'll do it.
No. I'm doing it. I
can fucking do it.
Hey. hey.
Oh. shit!
Hey. catch
that motherfucker.
Fuck!
Let's go.
Open it.
Okay. it's okay.
mate. What's going on?
Why have we stopped?
What's...
- Oh...
- Move.
You two. up there.
Sit down.
Keep your mouth shut.
Don't fucking move.
He needs that oxygen.
Fuck did I just say?
Can you hear me?
I know you helped break him out.
Where are they taking Sean?
I don't know.
Listen. I'm only gonna
ask you one more time.
But I don't know. I don't.
You can't just
turn that thing on.
Don't worry. I know
what I'm doing.
I told you...
I don't know anything.
I swear.
You'll kill him.
You'll
kill him like this!
- Fuck.
- Please...
Shh.
Where...
is he going?
Okay. okay. okay.
okay. okay. okay.
Please. please...
Close the door.
Someone's trying to frame
me for this cocaine spiking.
I had nothing to do with it.
I don't care.
Look. I really regret
what I did to you.
And I'm gonna make things right.
Just tell me what you want.
Car and some cash.
I don't have much time.
My car is up front.
you can take it.
There is money in the safe.
I know what I did was wrong.
I know.
You have no fucking idea.
I have to
get away from here.
But I'll be back.
I'll make things right with you.
I promise.
Liam. I know she's here.
- She's not here. Billy.
- Of course she's fucking here.
You're here. these
fucking goons are here.
Where the fuck else
is she gonna be?
I just need five
minutes with her.
I'm sorry.
You've heard the Albanians
have put a bounty
out on Sean's head. right?
He's been stitched up for a
spiking he didn't fucking do.
Now he's out there on his own
with no money and no phone.
Just give me a few of your
guys to help me go find him
because we need to
catch up with him
before someone else does.
You need to talk to
your mother about that.
That's what he's
trying to fucking do.
I'll tell her you called. Billy.
Fuck's sake.
Anything fucking happens to
Sean and you're to blame!
I told you we shouldn't
have fucking come here.
She'd never fucking help.
You fucking bitch!
Calm the fuck down.
Billy. Come on.
Hundreds have died.
Luan has lost a child.
All because of Sean.
Whatever happens
now is all on him.
They were taking
Sean to Greenwich.
so that's where he'll be headed.
Where abouts in Greenwich?
He didn't know.
I'll tell Faz and the
others to meet us there now.
Did you hear though?
Luan's put a bounty of two
million on Sean's head.
You fucking kidding me?
Elliot.
Luan. what part of
I need Sean alive...
Did you not understand?
I don't care what you
want or anyone else.
He killed my child.
So they're gonna pay for it.
Luan! Luan!
You got Sean?
I did. but he got away.
I shot him. so he won't be far.
I won't forget this. Lale.
Luan.
Just let me know when he's dead.
Oh. good.
He's waking up. Ronnie.
Took you a while. love.
Now. before you start whinging.
know that it's been
more than a decade
since I stitched up a
gunshot wound like that.
You're lucky she didn't
stitch your face to her arse.
Don't mind that codger.
He's just upset he can't
spend the whole day downstairs
in that bloody pub.
- Hmm.
- I've got tea on the stove for you.
- Grab me a biscuit. will ya?
- Grab it yourself.
You lazy sod.
Fucking old cow.
Are you trying to catch flies?
- Where am I?
- I found you passed out in the yard.
Thought you were legless.
till I saw all that blood.
I wanted to leave you there.
But the missus
wouldn't hear of it.
Here you go.
Where's me biscuit?
Milk or sugar?
Uh. what time is it?
- Six o'clock. love.
- Oh. shit.
You need to rest.
I need to get to Greenwich
as soon as possible.
Off you totter.
'Cause your mug's
all over the telly.
I don't care. I
need to get there.
Where's my gun?
No chance.
Ronnie will take you.
Why are you helping me?
There was a time when we
worshiped your father.
You speak for yourself.
Finn was
there for our oldest
when he got himself in a pickle.
Now we're repaying that debt.
Do you have a car?
A car?
We haven't driven in years.
But Ronnie worked
down the tunnels.
He knows all the shortcuts.
He can get you where
you need to go.
Seeing as I got
no say in nothing.
I'll just go and get
my coat then. will I?
Thanks.
Just so we're clear.
I don't want you going around
telling people we helped ya.
Me and the missus have got
enough problems as it is.
- Where are you taking me?
- To the gutter.
How long till
we get to Greenwich?
Rate you're moving.
about an hour.
Haven't got an hour.
You're welcome to get
the bus if you want.
Hold that. Turn it on.
I had that.
Move. move. move!
I'm looking for Sean Wallace.
We're not a missing
persons bureau.
If you want a drink. great.
Otherwise. you know
where the door is.
Hmm.
I've been standing up to bullies
long before you were even born.
He's with Ronnie.
They went down the tunnels.
Bravo.
Oh. here they are.
- About fucking time.
- We're waiting for one more.
Are you joking?
- We're on a tight window.
- He'll be here. Don't worry.
Look. I'm just saying. if we're
not ready to take off by seven...
I am in no mood for
windy cunts right now.
So fuck off.
What if he doesn't make it?
He'll make it.
Don't you worry.
The name Sean Wallace
still means something.
Somebody will help him.
All we've got to do now...
is hold our nerve.
Stick to the plan.
Get Sean out of here.
regroup. and then we'll
make all them cunts pay.
Sean... you... me...
Soon we're gonna be boss
in this fucking city.
Which bit of
Greenwich you after?
By the old
wharf. there's a pub.
Yeah. I know it.
What is this place?
You never took the tube
to your fancy private school then?
I know what the fucking
tube is. And it isn't this.
These are access tunnels.
Haven't been touched in decades.
You've got something
in common then.
Is it safe down here? Feels
like we might catch the plague.
Don't stick your cock in anything.
if that's what you're asking.
So what's the big plan. then?
Get to Ireland.
I've got family and friends
there who are willing to back me.
So you can return here.
and settle all your scores.
- Something like that.
- Mmm.
How do you know
about these tunnels?
Before I had the boozer.
I worked in sewage.
Not everyone's born a Wallace.
So how come
you knew my father?
I didn't.
But where do you
think his cronies
used to hide their
shite back in the day?
In shit.
Bingo.
Bodies. blow. you name it.
So you didn't
worship him then?
Deborah's
words. not mine.
Well. she said your son
got himself in a pickle.
Well. that's one
way of putting it.
He ran up drug debts and
your father wrote them off.
Is he okay now. your son?
He's dead.
Sorry.
I'm glad my father
wrote off his debt.
Yeah. Only after he put those drugs
on the street in the first place.
Why are you helping me.
- if that's how you feel?
- 'Cause the missus said so.
You do everything
the missus tells you?
I take it you've
never been married.
He's coming
here to Greenwich.
So I want all your
eyes on the street.
He might be in a car or on foot.
Whatever. I don't
care. I want him found.
and I want him alive.
- All right?
- Yes. boss.
- Go!
- Come on. you lot.
Jump in. Let's go. Come on.
What's wrong with your face?
Yo. if you've got
something to say. say it.
I hear you
about finding the guy.
- It just feels wrong.
- Which part?
Sean had your dad killed.
And my uncle.
Helping that piece of shit stay
alive just feels fucked up.
I say we kill him and we
just split that bounty.
My family were killed
in a hit and run...
by the same guy who killed the
driver that spiked the cocaine.
Hey. I'm sorry. but...
Elliot. what does that
have to do with Sean?
- He said it wasn't an accident.
- And you trust him?
What's to say he's not trying to
fuck with your mind right now?
Nothing.
But I can't risk finding
out that he isn't.
Please.
How much further?
It's not far.
Just...
Just give me a second.
You want some advice?
- Have I got a choice?
- Not really.
Enlighten me.
When you do get to
Ireland. just stay there.
Why?
Your father made it look easy
with all the charm and patter.
But to do what he did.
you have to be a right
proper cunt. too.
You think I can't be
a right proper cunt?
You don't fucking know me.
It's what my gut's telling me.
Let's get out
of this shit! Come on.
- Someone's coming.
- Come on. son. Let's move it.
Down here.
Come on. Let's move it. son.
To the left. there's a door
to the sewage system and out.
That will take you
where you need to be.
Come on! Over here.
Come on. get up! Get up.
Give me the keys. Quick.
- Which one?
- Silver one.
- Go and fuck yourself.
- Square.
Oh. fuck!
Come on! Move
in front. Do it!
Come on!
Get in. Quick!
Ronnie. Ronnie. come on.
No. go!
I'm all right.
Go. No!
- Come on! Come on!
- Go!
We have to go now or they
won't let us take off.
I told you. The window
closes at seven.
You'll fucking wait.
Stop. stop. stop. stop.
stop. There he is.
Sean. stop.
You're like a bad fucking penny.
Hey! What the fuck
are you doing?
Guys. we have to go now.
If you wanna get on that helicopter.
you tell me what I need to know.
What's his fucking name?
Tell me!
That's fucking Sean.
Come on.
Fuck.
- Who the fuck was that?
- I don't know.
Elliot! Elliot?
Hey. hey.
Hey.
Who the fuck are you?
What do you want?
Just tell me how much you want.
Name a figure and I'll pay.
I don't need your money.
Then what?
I can get you whatever you need.
Look at you now.
The great Sean Wallace.
I. uh...
I thought it'd be
difficult getting you here.
Piece of piss.
You're not so special.
Are you?
Five million.
Five million to let me go.
Ten million.
You can't kill me.
I'm a Wallace.
I'm Sean fucking Wallace!
I'm a proper fucking cunt!